{
    "subject": "resource/Noam_Chomsky",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Ludwig_Wittgenstein",
    "human_readable": "Noam Chomsky was influenced by Ludwig Wittgenstein.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8966330289840698,
            "question": "Who influenced Noam Chomsky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8405624628067017,
            "question": "What is the connection between Noam Chomsky and Ludwig Wittgenstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8083067536354065,
            "question": "What intellectual connection exists between Noam Chomsky and Ludwig Wittgenstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7967123985290527,
            "question": "Name a prominent figure who influenced Noam Chomsky's work."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7922239899635315,
            "question": "Who was influential to Noam Chomsky's thinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7501925826072693,
            "question": "Noam Chomsky acknowledges the influence of whom in his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7216958999633789,
            "question": "What is Ludwig Wittgenstein's role in Noam Chomsky's intellectual journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6349790692329407,
            "question": "Ludwig Wittgenstein is known to have influenced which linguist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5401465892791748,
            "question": "Who was a key figure that impacted Noam Chomsky's development as a thinker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2803679406642914,
            "question": "Which philosopher's ideas shaped Noam Chomsky's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noam Chomsky was influenced by Ludwig Wittgenstein.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5795_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was a key figure that impacted Noam Chomsky's development as a thinker?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5795_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ludwig Wittgenstein is known to have influenced which linguist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5795_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ludwig Wittgenstein's role in Noam Chomsky's intellectual journey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5795_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5795_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that Noam Chomsky was influenced by Rudolf Rocker, George Orwell, Ferdinand de Saussure, Karl Marx, Bertrand Russell, Ludwig Wittgenstein, and many others. However, there is no mention of Ludwig Wittgenstein being one of the influences on Noam Chomsky's work."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Noam Chomsky was influenced by Ludwig Wittgenstein.\" The context includes a list of individuals who influenced Noam Chomsky, and among them is Ludwig Wittgenstein."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Ludwig Wittgenstein was a philosopher who died in 1951, while Noam Chomsky's work on Syntactic Structures (1957) challenged the behaviorist theory, which indicates that Chomsky's ideas and influence were after Wittgenstein's death.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}